Guide to the Records of the NYU TV and Media Services Video Recordings RG.38.16.1
New York University Archives
- Series I: Video Recordings, 1993-2005
  - NYU Press Book Spots, undated; cuid903; 1 videocassettes (Box 60)
  - Industry Attractions, undated; cuid904; 1 U-matic (Box 103)
  - "(Your Name Here)", Oct 1994; cuid905; 2 videocassettes (Box 60, Box 103)
  - Science at New York University, April 1994; cuid906; 1 VHS (Box 60)
  - Festival Spring Orchestra and Symphony Orchestra Fall Concert, 24 Nov 1998; cuid907; 1 Betamax (Box 61)
  - The City and the University, 26 Sep 1994; cuid908; 1 Betamax (Box 61)
  - Save the Day Mathematics Education: The Debate Over the Standards Tape 1, Undated; cuid909; 1 Betamax (Box 61)
  - The Artist as Advocate Tape 2, 6 Oct 1998; cuid910; 1 Betamax (Box 61)
  - Ann Linnchan Roll-Ins, undated; cuid911; 1 Betamax (Box 61)
  - Olympics Opening Ceremony, 15 Sep 2000; cuid912; 3 VHS (Box 61)
  - Library Success in the New World, 23 April 2000; cuid913; 1 VHS (Box 62)
  - In Our Own Words, undated; cuid914; 1 VHS (Box 62)
  - On our Own Terms: Moyers on Dying, 18 April 2000; cuid915; 1 VHS (Box 62)
  - New York University Tonight Election 2000, cuid916; 1 VHS (Box 62)
  - New York University Celebrates 2000, cuid917; 1 VHS (Box 104)
  - NYU Law School: Rally against Impeachment, 14 Dec 1998; cuid918; 2 VHS (Box 61)
  - African Studies Readings, 1998-2000; cuid919; 3 Betamax (Box 61)
  - Mental Health in the Year 2010, 1 April 1998; cuid920; 2 Betamax (Box 61)
  - New York University Press Awards, 18 April 2000; cuid921; 1 Betamax (Box 61)
  - New Open, 3 Nov 1995; cuid922; 1 Betamax (Box 62)
  - Dr. Judy at Radio Station Z-100, 25 Sep 1996; cuid923; 1 Betamax (Box 62)
  - Ed Koch Lecture, undated; cuid924; 1 Betamax (Box 62)
  - Promo Masters, 21 June 1995; cuid925; 1 Betamax (Box 62)
  - New York University TV News, undated; cuid926; 1 Betamax (Box 62)
  - Anniversary of Attica Riots, 1996; cuid927; 2 videocassettes (Box 62)
  - "Advances in Science" U-matic, undated; cuid928 (Box 62)
  - "Corporate Takeover of News: Blunting the Sword" U-matic, 8 Oct 1996; cuid929 (Box 62)
  - "The Electric Blanket" U-matic, undated; cuid930 (Box 62)
  - NYU University Week Wide of Service, undated; cuid931; 1 U-matic (Box 62)
  - STU Camera 1 Shimon Peres, undated; cuid932; 2 Betamax (Box 62)
  - "Sheer Realities" at Grey Art Gallery B-Roll of exhbit and exhibit Voice overs, 28 Feb 2000; cuid933; 5 videocassettes (Box 64)
  - "Bamboozled" NYU Institute of African American Affairs, 2 Nov 2000; cuid934; 2 videocassettes (Box 64)
  - Doctor Ruth, 01 Nov 1995; cuid935; 1 videocassettes (Box 64)
  - Dr. Ferrara at NYU, 2000; cuid936; 3 videocassettes (Box 64)
  - Inverted Odysseys, 22 Nov 1999; cuid937; 4 videocassettes (Box 64)
  - Faculty Focus Interviews: McSorleys, Village Writers, Great Depression, undated; cuid938; 1 videocassettes (Box 64)
  - "Jump Tomorrow" Joel Hopkins and Tundi Adibimpe, 17 Jul 2001; cuid939; 2 videocassettes (Box 64, Box 85)
  - Panel Discussion Art and Alternative Media, 7 Feb 1998; cuid940; 1 videocassettes (Box 104)
  - "Accidental Human Presence in the Age of Bacteria" Steven J. Gould, 16 Oct 1996; cuid941; 1 videocassettes (Box 104)
  - Bradford Marshalls Interview, undated; cuid942; 1 videocassettes (Box 64)
  - Integrating Media and Instruction, 1994; cuid943; 1 videocassettes (Box 104)
  - "A Night of Langston Hughes" with Danny Glover and Ossie Davis, undated; cuid944; 1 videocassettes (Box 104)
  - Dale Russakoff Speech, 3 Jun 1999; cuid945; 1 videocassettes (Box 64)
  - "Irish Paintings" Grey Art Gallery, 29 Jun 1999; cuid946; 1 videocassettes (Box 64)
  - Walter Mosley and Ranall Robinson at NYU Law, 10 Feb 2000; cuid947; 2 videocassettes (Box 83)
  - NYU Law Panel #3, 21 Sep 1998; cuid948; 3 videocassettes (Box 65)
  - Morning on the Millenium Panel, 14 Apr 2000; cuid949; 3 videocassettes (Box 65)
  - Democracy and the Rule of Law in a Changing World, 10 Mar 2000; cuid950; 4 videocassettes (Box 65)
  - Hartford Institute for Geriatric Nursing Development, 2 Jun 1999; cuid951; 1 videocassettes (Box 65)
  - My Country vs ME, 13 Feb 2002; cuid952; 1 videocassettes (Box 66)
  - Art Museums and the Public Trust: A Deontological, 8 Apr 2003; cuid953; 1 videocassettes (Box 66)
  - A Evening with Marvin J. Miller, 21 May 2003; cuid954; 1 videocassettes (Box 66)
  - "Marketing on the Internet" Evening Lecture Series, 7 Oct 1999; cuid955; 5 videocassettes (Box 66, Box 69)
  - Merryl Lynch Digital Lecture, 23 Jan 2000; cuid956; 1 videocassettes (Box 65)
  - Our Democracy, Our Airways, 30 Sep 2002; cuid957; 1 videocassettes (Box 66)
  - "2001 Mayors Election Conference", 8 Nov 2001; cuid958; 1 videocassettes (Box 66)
  - "Rekindling Reform", 10 Mar 2003; cuid959; 1 videocassettes (Box 66)
  - "Real Anatomy: Frumkes and O'Neil", 18 Nov 2002; cuid960; 1 videocassettes (Box 66)
  - Raineri Lecture in Ancient Studies, 13 Jun 2001; cuid961; 1 videocassettes (Box 66)
  - ACH-ALLC 2001 Conference, 13 Jun 2001; cuid962; 1 videocassettes (Box 66)
  - Teaching More Effectively with Technology, 11 Apr 2001; cuid963; 3 videocassettes (Box 66)
  - Cirriculum Base Parent Program, 9 Mar 2001; cuid964; 1 videocassettes (Box 66)
  - 1 Commerce, 6 Apr 2001; cuid965; 1 videocassettes (Box 66)
  - Progress and Paradox: The Realities of Globalization, 14 Jan 2003; cuid966; 4 videocassettes (Box 66)
  - Julian Schnabel Interview, 7 Oct 2001; cuid967; 4 videocassettes (Box 66)
  - Dean's Day, 5 Apr 2003; cuid968; 4 videocassettes (Box 66)
  - At Your Library - Nancy Kranich, 14 Mar 2001; cuid969; 1 videocassettes (Box 66)
  - Beowolf Shoot, unknown; cuid970; 1 videocassettes (Box 66)
  - The Alger Hiss Story, 21 Mar 2001; cuid971; 1 videocassettes (Box 66)
  - September 11, Announcements John Bleckman, 11 Sep 2001; cuid972; 1 videocassettes (Box 66)
  - President's Welcome 2005, 5 Sep 2005; cuid973; 1 videocassettes (Box 69)
  - Looking Back, Looking Beyond, 25 Sep 2003; cuid974; 3 videocassettes (Box 69)
  - Ultraviolet Live 2005, 1 Mar 2005; cuid975; 9 videocassettes (Box 69)
  - Absintee Father, 16 Feb 2001; cuid976; 1 videocassettes (Box 69)
  - Bobst 30th Anniversary, undated; cuid977; 1 videocassettes (Box 69)
  - Asian Cultural Expressions Promo, 1 Jan 2002; cuid978; 1 videocassettes (Box 66)
  - Campus Flash: Community Service 9/11 Educare, undated; cuid979; 4 videocassettes (Box 69)
  - Campus Flash: Community Service Interviews, undated; cuid980; 1 videocassettes (Box 69)
  - "A/P/A studies" Hmong Man, 18 Feb 2005; cuid981; 1 videocassettes (Box 66)
  - Bobst Interiors, 26 August 1994; cuid982; 1 videocassettes (Box 69)
  - Gallatin: Dedication, 12 Oct 1995; cuid983; 1 videocassettes (Box 66)
  - King Hussein of Jordan at Bobst Library, 6 Oct 1996; cuid984; 1 videocassettes (Box 66)
  - Attica 25 Anniversary Live Feed from Loeb, 9 Apr 1997; cuid985; 2 videocassettes (Box 66)
  - King Juan Carlos Dedication, 9 Apr 1997; cuid986; 1 videocassettes (Box 66)
  - Ann Linnehan: Teleconference Opening Interview, 10 Feb 1997; cuid987; 1 videocassettes (Box 69)
  - NYU Park Clean Up, 21 Apr 1998; cuid988; 1 videocassettes (Box 69)
  - JS Sargent, 1999 Sep 13; cuid989; 2 videocassettes (Box 67)
  - Queen Sofia Slate, 31 Oct 2004; cuid990; 5 videocassettes (Box 67, Box 85)
  - NYU TV News at Noon: Morley Safer, 17 Oct 1995; cuid991; 5 videocassettes (Box 67, Box 85)
  - Gallatin: Blues Event for African American History, undated; cuid992; 1 videocassettes (Box 85)
  - The Good, The Bad, and the Ugly, undated; cuid993; 1 videocassettes (Box 67)
  - Bobcat System, undated; cuid994; 1 videocassettes (Box 85)
  - "In Our Own Words" Lecture Panel, undated; cuid995; 1 videocassettes
  - Jump Tomorrow, 17 Jul 2001; cuid996; 2 videocassettes (Box 67)
  - Coles: Fencing, Swimming, Women's Basketball, undated; cuid997; 1 videocassettes (Box 67)
  - Livewire with Nelly Music, undated; cuid998; 1 videocassettes (Box 67)
  - Dental School Project: David B Kriser, 1 Jan 1994; cuid999; 1 videocassettes (Box 67)
  - Domestic and Family Violence in the 21st Century, 2 Feb 2001; cuid1000; 5 videocassettes (Box 67, Box 85)
  - KRS 1: Interview of Gild Green, 12 Feb 1998; cuid1001; 1 videocassettes (Box 67)
  - Happy Birthday Bobst, 30 Nov 1994; cuid1002; 1 videocassettes (Box 85)
  - 4th Annual Irwin Mann Memorial Lecture on Voting, undated; cuid1003; 1 videocassettes (Box 67)
  - Verdi Conference, 21 Aug 2001; cuid1004; 6 videocassettes (Box 67, Box 85)
  - DHHS Teleconference for Presidents Initiative, undated; cuid1005; 1 videocassettes (Box 67)
  - Genital Dermotology: STD's, 9 Mar 2003; cuid1006; 1 videocassettes (Box 67)
  - Laboratory Procedure in Fixed Prostheodontics, undated; cuid1007; 1 videocassettes (Box 85)
  - ALA Presidential Candidates Forum, 12 Mar 1999; cuid1008; 1 videocassettes (Box 67)
  - Presidents Service Awards, 6 Apr 1999; cuid1009; 1 videocassettes (Box 67)
  - Soaring to Excellance Teleconference, 1 Jan 1999; cuid1010; 1 videocassettes (Box 67)
  - 110th Anniversary Celebrationg of Naming Education, 5 Apr 2001; cuid1011; 1 videocassettes (Box 68)
  - Lewis Burke Frumkes Lecture in Philosophy, 13 Nov 2000; cuid1012; 1 videocassettes (Box 68)
  - Psychological Disabilites on Campus, 2 Apr 2001; cuid1013; 1 videocassettes (Box 68)
  - Anthrax: What Every Clinician Should Know, 2 Apr 2001; cuid1014; 1 videocassettes (Box 68)
  - Institute of French Studies: Deconstruction, 8 Oct 1993; cuid1015; 1 videocassettes (Box 68)
  - Realities and Reintegration: Multi Dimensional, 1 Jan 2000; cuid1016; 1 videocassettes (Box 68)
  - Economics and Entrepreneuship Conference Session, undated; cuid1017; 8 videocassettes (Box 68)
  - Morning on the Millenium Panel, 14 Apr 2000; cuid1018; 2 videocassettes (Box 68)
  - Reflections on the Tradgedy, 18 Sep 2001; cuid1019; 8 videocassettes (Box 68)
  - Reflections on the Tradgedy - Seminar 3, 24 Sep 2001; cuid1020; 1 videocassettes (Box 68)
  - Democracy and the Rule of Law in a Changing World, 7 March 2000; cuid1021; 1 videocassettes (Box 68)
  - What Now?: Foreign Policy Lectures, 10 May 2003; cuid1022; 1 videocassettes (Box 68)
  - Campaign Finance and the Law and Political Campaign, 29 Nov 2001; cuid1023; 2 videocassettes (Box 68)
  - The Employment Intervention Demonstration, 18 Jan 2002; cuid1024; 1 videocassettes (Box 68)
  - Immunization Update 2001, cuid1025; 2 videocassettes (Box 68)
  - Barabara Goldsmith Preservation Lecture Series, 24 Jun 2002; cuid1026; 1 videocassettes (Box 68)
  - Autumn Festival, undated; cuid1027; 1 videocassettes (Box 68)
  - Fast Food: Susan Landau, undated; cuid1028; 1 videocassettes (Box 83)
  - School of Education Policy Breakfast, 26 Dec 2000; cuid1029; 1 videocassettes (Box 68)
  - US VS Microsoft, 5 May 2000; cuid1030; 1 videocassettes (Box 85)
  - US VS Microsoft - From a Legal Perspective, 5 May 2000; cuid1031; 1 videocassettes (Box 68)
  - US VS Microsoft - From an Economic Perspective, 5 May 2000; cuid1032; 1 videocassettes (Box 68)
  - US VS Microsoft - Panel Discussion, 5 May 2000; cuid1033; 1 videocassettes (Box 68)
  - The World of Electron Commerce, 27 Feb 2000; cuid1034; 1 videocassettes (Box 68)
  - CAS Scholar in Residence Lecture: David M., 11 Mar 2008; cuid1035; 1 MiniDV (Box 69)
  - Conversations with Champions of Moral Courage, 11 Mar 2008; cuid1036; 6 videocassettes (Box 69)
  - Social Entrepreneuership in the 12st Century, 5 Mar 2008; cuid1037; 1 videocassettes (Box 69)
  - Institute of African American Affairs: Artist in Residence, April 2007; cuid1038; 3 videocassettes (Box 69)
  - New York Metropolitan Transportation Council Public Meeting, 13 Mar 2008; cuid1039; 1 DVCAM (Box 69)
  - The Dead Sea Scrolls at 60: Keynote Address, 6 Mar 2008; cuid1040; 2 DVCAM (Box 69)
  - The Dead Sea Scrolls at 60: Keynote Address, 6 Mar 2008; cuid1041; 1 DVD-R (Box 69)
  - The Dead Sea Scrolls at 60: Session 1 - Rewriting, 6 Mar 2008; cuid1042; 2 DVCAM (Box 69)
  - The Dead Sea Scrolls at 60: Session 1 - Rewriting, 6 Mar 2008; cuid1043; 1 DVD-R (Box 69)
  - The Dead Sea Scrolls at 60: Session 2 - The Dead, 6 Mar 2008; cuid1044; 2 DVCAM (Box 69)
  - The Dead Sea Scrolls at 60: Session 2 - The Dead, 6 Mar 2008; cuid1045; 2 DVD-R (Box 69)
  - The Dead Sea Scrolls at 60: Sesson 3 - The Scrolls, 7 Mar 2008; cuid1046; 2 DVCAM (Box 69)
  - The Dead Sea Scrolls at 60: Sesson 3 - The Scrolls, 7 Mar 2008; cuid1047; 1 DVD-R (Box 69)
  - The Dead Sea Scrolls at 60: Session 4 - Judaen, 7 Mar 2008; cuid1048; 1 DVCAM (Box 69)
  - The Dead Sea Scrolls at 60: Session 4 - Judaen, 7 Mar 2008; cuid1049; 2 DVD-R (Box 69)
  - Dan William Memorial, 6 April 2008; cuid1050; 1 DVCAM (Box 69)
  - Moving Images: Preserving Down Fales Preservation Panels, 4 Apr 2008; cuid1051; 2 DVCAM (Box 69)
  - A Night of Disney Music, 3 Apr 2008; cuid1052; 2 MiniDV (Box 69)
  - Master Chef 2008 - Delicious Duo Raw Footage, 28 Mar 2008; cuid1053; 3 MiniDV (Box 69)
  - Master Chef 2008 - Interviews Raw Footage, 28 Mar 2008; cuid1054; 5 MiniDV (Box 69)
  - Master Chef 2008 - Omnivores Raw Footage, 28 Mar 2008; cuid1055; 2 MiniDV (Box 69)
  - Master Chef 2008 - Campus Flash, 28 Mar 2008; cuid1056; 1 MiniDV (Box 69)
  - A Breath of Wok: The French Culinary A/P/A, 4 Nov 2004; cuid1057; 2 MiniDV (Box 69)
  - Master's Program in Global Public Health Panel Lecture, 25 Apr 2008; cuid1058; 1 MiniDV (Box 69)
  - National Public Policy Forum Semi-Final, 26 Apr 2008; cuid1059; 2 DVD-R (Box 69)
  - National Public Policy Forum Final Debate, 26 Apr 2008; cuid1060; 1 DVD-R (Box 69)
  - College of Arts and Science Reality Show, 29 Aug 2004; cuid1061; 3 MiniDV (Box 69)
  - Global Public Health: Paul Farmer, 30 Apr 2008; cuid1062; 2 MiniDV (Box 69)
  - "ISO Camera" Cohen-Nunn Dialogues, 28 Apr 2008; cuid1063; 4 videocassettes (Box 69)
  - Dr. James Watson Lecture, 30 Apr 2008; cuid1064; 2 MiniDV (Box 69)
  - "Global Public Health" Student Presentations, 1 May 2008; cuid1065; 1 MiniDV (Box 69)
  - "Issues, Challenges and Triumphs: Creating an Action Agenda for the Black and Latino Male in America" Kimmel Center, 18 Feb 2008; cuid1066; 2 MiniDV (Box 69)
  - "The Enduring Impact..." Fales Food Series James Beard Discussion, 1 May 2008; cuid1067; 1 MiniDV (Box 69)
  - "A Tribute to Dr. Bob Kevesh" Kavesh Reception, 14 May 2008; cuid1068; 1 DVCAM (Box 69)
  - The 5th Annual Vernice Ferguson Colloquium, 17 May 2008; cuid1069; 1 DVCAM (Box 69)
  - Zuckerman Forum Quarterfinals, 19 Apr 2007; cuid1070; 3 MiniDV (Box 69)
  - Zuckerman Forum Quarterfinals, 19 Apr 2007; cuid1071; 1 DVD-R (Box 69)
  - Zuckerman Forum Semifinals, 19 Apr 2007; cuid1072; 3 DVD-R (Box 69)
  - Zuckerman Forum Semifinals, 19 Apr 2007; cuid1073; 1 MiniDV (Box 69)
  - "Danger Opportunity Musing on Risk" Stern Alumni Business Conference, 16 May 2008; cuid1074; 1 MiniDV (Box 69)
  - "The Future of Stern" Stern Alumni Business Conference, 16 May 2008; cuid1075; 2 MiniDV (Box 69)
  - "The Digital Future..." Stern Alumni Business Conference, 16 May 2008; cuid1076; 1 DVCAM (Box 69)
  - "Venture Capital" Stern Alumni Business Conference, 16 May 2008; cuid1077; 1 DVCAM (Box 69)
  - Room 914 Plenary Session - Stern Alumni Business Conference, 16 May 2008; cuid1078; 3 DVCAM (Box 69)
  - "A Mexican Experiance in the Care of Audiovisual Collections and Archives" Fernando Osokio MIAP Fall 2005 Speaker Series, 14 Oct 2005; cuid1079; 1 videocassettes (Box 69)
  - Presidents Welcome 2006, 28 Aug 2006; cuid1080; 1 MiniDV (Box 69)
  - Water: A Global Discussion of a Critical Topic, 5 June 2008; cuid1081; 1 DVCAM (Box 69)
  - Justice Now! Organizing Immigrant Communities, 31 March 2007; cuid1082; 3 MiniDV (Box 70)
  - Forte Foundation B Roll and Webcast, 22 June 2007; cuid1083; 4 DVD-R (Box 70)
  - Forte Foundation B Roll and Webcast, 22 June 2007; cuid1084; 1 DVCAM (Box 70)
  - NYU Symphony Orchestra Field Tapes, undated; cuid1085; 4 DVCAM (Box 70)
  - "Scientific Methods: Survival Skills" Panel Presentation, 24 Feb 2007; cuid1086; 1 DVCAM (Box 70)
  - "Scientific Methods: Survival Skills - Literature" Panel Presentation, 24 Feb 2007; cuid1087; 1 DVCAM (Box 70)
  - "Scientific Methods: Survival Skills - Scientific Writing" Panel Presentation, 24 Feb 2007; cuid1088; 1 DVCAM (Box 70)
  - "Scientific Methods: Survival Skills - Oral Presentation" Panel Presentation, 24 Feb 2007; cuid1089; 1 DVCAM (Box 70)
  - Albert Gallatin Lecture Series "An Evening with Sally Field", 16 Apr 2007; cuid1090; 1 DVCAM (Box 70)
  - Wagner Capstone Project Presentations Event, 1 Apr 2007; cuid1091; 1 MiniDV (Box 70)
  - 2nd Annual Zuckerman Forum Finals, 24 Apr 2007; cuid1092; 1 DVCAM (Box 70)
  - 2nd Annual Zuckerman Forum Finals, 24 Apr 2007; cuid1093; 1 DVD-R (Box 70)
  - "Master Chef" Contest, 26 Feb 2007; cuid1094; 8 MiniDV (Box 70)
  - Paul Farmer: Social Entrepreneurship in the 21st Century"= Social Reynolds Speaker Series, 8 May 2007; cuid1095; 1 DVCAM (Box 70)
  - "The Artist in Residence" The Institute of African American Affair's, 17 Apr 2007; cuid1096; 1 DVCAM (Box 70)
  - "Global Crisis in the Nursing Workforce", 1 Oct 2007; cuid1097; 2 MiniDV (Box 70)
  - Presidential Welcome 2007, 27 Aug 2007; cuid1098; 1 MiniDV (Box 70)
  - "Midwife Conversation" School of Nursing, 24 Aug 2007; cuid1099; 1 MiniDV (Box 70)
  - "SMPTE NY" at Cantor Film Center, 6 Jun 2007; cuid1100; 1 DVCAM (Box 70)
  - Steinhardt Faculty Concert, 10 Sep 2007; cuid1101; 3 DVCAM (Box 70)
  - All Library Staff Meeting with Dean Carol Mandel, 31 May 2007; cuid1102; 1 DVCAM (Box 70)
  - "Reality Show" program, 31 Aug 2007; cuid1103; 4 DVCAM (Box 70)
  - Jason Stanyek Lecture, 11 May 2007; cuid1104; 19 MiniDV (Box 70)
  - "Sustainable Agriculture" Fales Food Program, 25 Jul 2007; cuid1105; 1 DVCAM (Box 70)
  - Reynolds Speaker Series: Fazle Hasan, 21 Sep 2007; cuid1106; 2 MiniDV (Box 70)
  - Master Chef Samples, 1 Jan 2007; cuid1107; 1 DVD-R (Box 70)
  - Welcome Week 2007, 31 Aug 2007; cuid1108; 5 MiniDV (Box 70)
  - "Further Adventures in Legal" Law School, 20 Jun 2007; cuid1109; 1 DVCAM (Box 70)
  - Global Mitigation, 25 Apr 2006; cuid1110; 2 MiniDV (Box 70)
  - "Interview with Jaime" Video Art Interviews, 10 Oct 2007; cuid1111; 4 DVCAM (Box 70)
  - VLAL Step-up B-Roll, 8 Oct 2007; cuid1112; 1 MiniDV (Box 70)
  - "Global Public Health: Dead Mums Don't Cry", 9 oct 2007; cuid1113; 2 MiniDV (Box 70)
  - "Where Farmers Grow" Fales Food Series, 11 Oct 2007; cuid1114; 1 DVCAM (Box 70)
  - NYU Abu Dhabi at the Greenburg Lounge, 12 Oct 2007; cuid1115; 1 DVCAM (Box 70)
  - CAS's Parent's Event, 20 Oct 2007; cuid1116; 1 MiniDV (Box 70)
  - Bio-Ethics Conference, 20 Oct 2007; cuid1117; 5 DVCAM (Box 70)
  - Colloquium on the Supreme Court Case, 24 Oct 2007; cuid1118; 1 DVCAM (Box 70)
  - Liberia Lecture, undated; cuid1119; 1 MiniDV (Box 70)
  - The 8th Annual Lewis Burke Frumkes Lecture, 29 Oct 2007; cuid1120; 1 DVCAM (Box 70)
  - The Ignaugural Jacob K. Javits Lecture, 29 Oct 2007; cuid1121; 1 DVCAM (Box 70)
  - Social Entreprenuership in the 21st Century with J.B. Schramm, 30 Oct 2007; cuid1122; 2 MiniDV (Box 70)
  - College of Nursing Studio Interviews, 2 Nov 2007; cuid1123; 2 MiniDV (Box 70)
  - Steinhardt Jazz Symphony Anycast Shoot, 26 Oct 2007; cuid1124; 6 videocassettes (Box 70)
  - SCPS Media Talk in Tishman Auditorium, 7 Nov 2007; cuid1125; 4 DVCAM (Box 70)
  - Rudin Center for Transporation Conference, 13 Nov 2007; cuid1126; 1 DVCAM (Box 70)
  - Steinhardt Department of Music "Piano Inter-Studio", 19 Nov 2007; cuid1127; 4 DVCAM (Box 70)
  - All University Sing, 9 Dec 1997; cuid1128; 2 videocassettes (Box 95)
  - The NYU Festival String Orchestra, 11 Mar 1998; cuid1129; 1 Betacam (Box 71)
  - Yale Storm and Hot Pastrami, 4 Nov 1998; cuid1130; 1 Betacam (Box 71)
  - Education Policy Breakfast "Black and White Acheivement", Unknown; cuid1131; 1 DVCAM (Box 71)
  - Educational Policy Breakfast "Does Money Matter?", 22 Mar 2001; cuid1132; 1 DVCAM (Box 71)
  - Educational Policy Breakfast "Closing the Achievement Gap", 13 Dec 2001; cuid1133; 1 DVCAM (Box 71)
  - Educational Policy Breakfast "An Instructional Vision", 12 Dec 2001; cuid1134; 2 MiniDV (Box 71)
  - Educational Policy Breakfast "The Purpose of Education", 25 Mar 2002; cuid1135; 1 DVCAM (Box 71)
  - Educational Policy Breakfast "Mathematics: Clear or Fuzzy?", 29 Apr 2003; cuid1136; 1 DVCAM (Box 71)
  - Educational Policy Breakfast "Gender Implications", 5 Apr 2000; cuid1137; 1 DVCAM (Box 95)
  - Installation of the 15th President, 26 Sep 2002; cuid1138; 1 DVCAM (Box 95)
  - Bobst Library, 28 Apr 1998; cuid1139; 2 Betacam (Box 71)
  - President Oliva Promotes New York University TV, 8 Aug 1995; cuid1140; 1 Betacam (Box 71)
  - Hang Blix: Disarming Iraq, 15 Mar 2004; cuid1141; 1 DVCAM (Box 71)
  - "Critical Topics in Food" Fales Series, 17 May 2005; cuid1142; 2 DVCAM (Box 71, Box 95)
  - A Lecture with Helen Zia "Colliding into 2020", 5 October 2004; cuid1143; 1 DVCAM (Box 71)
  - Amy Goodman, 24 Feb 2004; cuid1144; 2 MiniDV (Box 71)
  - Lewis Burke Frumkes Lecture in Philiosophy Noam Chomsky, 15 Nov 2004; cuid1145; 1 DVCAM (Box 71)
  - Bobst Library Anniversary, 16 Dec 2002; cuid1146; 1 DVCAM (Box 95)
  - Susana Baca, 15 July 2003; cuid1147; 1 DVCAM (Box 71)
  - Lewis Burke Frumkes Lecture in Philosophy Peter Singer, 17 Nov 2003; cuid1148; 1 DVCAM (Box 71)
  - MIAP Speakers Series: Dan Streible, 19 Nov 2004; cuid1149; 1 DVCAM (Box 71)
  - Fales Library Series: Marvin Taylor, 12 Feb 2003; cuid1150; 2 MiniDV (Box 71, Box 95)
  - Hugh Masereld and Harry Belefonte in Conversation, 22 Feb 2005; cuid1151; 2 MiniDV (Box 71)
  - Scholars and Artists Episode 1, 20 Jan 2005; cuid1152; 8 DVCAM (Box 71)
  - David Wojnarowicz and Peter Hujar, 20 Sep 2005; cuid1153; 1 DVCAM (Box 71)
  - John Kerry Lecture, 20 Sep 2004; cuid1154; 1 DVCAM (Box 71)
  - Wagner School, 11 Oct 2000; cuid1155; 1 MiniDV (Box 95)
  - Charlie Rose Lecture, 21 Nov 2003; cuid1156; 2 DVCAM (Box 71)
  - Jay Oliva Portrait Unveiling, 5 May 2003; cuid1157; 1 MiniDV (Box 95)
  - Fales Lecture Series "Up is up, But So Is Down", 26 Oct 2006; cuid1158; 1 MiniDV (Box 71)
  - Robert Preston Tisch Dinner, 26 Jan 2006; cuid1159; 1 videocassettes (Box 71)
  - Skirball Center Ribbon Cutting Ceremony, 2 Oct 2003; cuid1160; 1 MiniDV (Box 71)
  - Skirball Center Ribbon Cutting Ceremony, 2 Oct 2003; cuid1161; 2 DVCAM (Box 71)
  - TV 37 Clone Music, undated; cuid1162; 1 MiniDV (Box 71)
  - Kimmel Exterior Station ID, undated; cuid1163; 1 MiniDV (Box 71)
  - Kimmel Ribbon Cutting Ceremony, 11 Jun 2003; cuid1164; 1 DVCAM (Box 71)
  - Puck Building Dedication and Debate, 23 Sep 2004; cuid1165; 2 MiniDV (Box 71)
  - Hannah Kohn Tabacco Use Lecture, 30 Oct 2001; cuid1166; 1 MiniDV (Box 71)
  - SS Proleterka Reading by Feur Jaeggy, 9 Dec 2003; cuid1167; 2 MiniDV (Box 71)
  - America and Islam in a Global World, 24 Jan 2002; cuid1168; 5 Betacam (Box 72)
  - America and Islam in a Global World, 24 Jan 2002; cuid1169; 1 DVCAM (Box 72)
  - Domestic and Family Violence in the 21st Century, 2 Feb 2001; cuid1170; 6 VHS (Box 72)
  - Carol Gilligan "Understanding Gender", 5 Apr 2000; cuid1171; 1 Betacam (Box 72)
  - NYU Development Dr. Epstein Surgery, 26 Oct 1995; cuid1172; 1 Betacam (Box 72)
  - Harold Levy Lecture, 26 Apr 2000; cuid1173; 1 VHS (Box 72)
  - John Lang and Todd Gitlin, 1 Dec 1998; cuid1174; 4 Betacam (Box 73)
  - Spike Lee Black Genuis, 8 Oct 1998; cuid1175; 2 Betacam (Box 73)
  - Downtown Poetry Reading at Fales Library, 27 Oct 1998; cuid1176; 1 videocassettes (Box 73)
  - African American Trade Unions at Bobst Library, 10 Feb 2000; cuid1177; 2 Betacam (Box 73)
  - Dennis Cooper Panel, 2 Mar 2000; cuid1178; 2 Betacam (Box 73)
  - New York University TV Alumni Interview Brian Frazee, 26 Aug 1998; cuid1179; 7 Betacam (Box 80)
  - NYU Celebrates Africana Studies, 25 Sep 1998; cuid1180; 1 Betacam (Box 73)
  - Carol Gilligan "Understanding Gender", 2 Apr 2000; cuid1181; 1 Betacam (Box 73)